sup everyone team is looking for five
here with a very special video today
have you ever thought to yourself damn
there is a lot of popsicles in the world
in the world a lot of colors too and
each color represents a Sonic unknown
character
damn but which one's the best I think
that every day of my life so i
know you do too and you and you we all
think that
so I thought it would be awesome to make
a t-list and my word is the right one
about what is the best flavor of the
rainbow delicious soccer and I see
popsicles
now these are already getting melt i
just took them out of the freezer so
they're nice and cold and and i'll
start with the one that we already know
the cherry popsicle this is the most
basic ass
on the planet
now not saying that's a bad thing
in fact
that's pretty damn good
i mean we all had a popsicle like this
one
this is the top popsicle you get
when you go to like an ice cream truck
and this is the one for 50 cents if
your mama won't give you two bucks
you're stuck with the red one now again
that's that might be a good thing
because everyone likes it no one you
can't really hate this popsicle
so honestly
i gotta put that smack in the middle for
now because that's like a b rank if you
hate it you're on but if you say to the
best in the world no one believes you
get the out of here go on to
another color
oh
now this
this is some special
this is like if you got a sugar daddy
and he wants to he wants he wants to
spoil you a bit sprinkle some of them
corns in your butt cracking
that's a good one
that is like rock raspberry get
this one shouldn't even be here with the
bloom
that's song that's like your sucking
socks balls
these are like your sucking Knuckles
balls but
why would you suck Knuckles balls when
socks got the big ass you know what i
mean
going on to the next one we are going to
do I really wanna you know I gotta i
gotta go I gotta go with the game gotta
go with socks bro
this one
this is another this is that's a little
bit of orange I hate on you know
I'm going I'm going straight to Mindy no
one likes if you tell me
that you get ospots and grape and orange
these two don't equally um a meat on the
last ones left in amigo the bomb
I'm not even gonna taste this one if you
think I am going to put
a popsicle that makes me think of
miniature the in my Goddamn
mouth
you got nothing coming
I'm not doing that I ain't like that
I'm that's going to the bottom
go on to the next once one
i gotta do this queen lena your pop
still sucks no one likes grape
no one does as a fact orange and grape
these are the two that always ends up in
your freezer for days
you don't want that no one likes that
i don't need a popsicle that resembles a
slot you know what I mean
you don't want it I'm going back to this
one
that's a good popsicle this one's good
too
that's cool
oh yeah
oh there's a yellow on that green one
i'll put that one like I gotta put bro
what I want the yellow one now
oh yeah
um
now yellow
this is the sugar dye
this one is that what your daddy sugar
daddy will buy for you at that's good
but he's just going to buy this one for
himself
um
this is a good one
just look up
there's like a diamond
look zero excess
dark shines
my bow is frozen piss hmm
that's that's that's what I like to see
so this is everyone this is the official
ranking of the official soccer ass pop
tlist sorry there's no yellow cop at all
that one
but in last place you got Mindy little
then queen lina
then mag that dog the Knuckles that
kidna
Hedgehog then the sexy man himself by
Montclair of Dresden
remember to comment like and subscribe
and leave a comment
about what your favorite ice pop is
I'm sorry to yo one but
shout out to you some imagination bit
what's your second favorite one